I was told that she was found in the kibbutz and she was found dead but in
actual fact it was a mistake she wasn't found it I was I was relieved I was
relieved that she was dead and it was all it was all over it would have been
pretty quick yeah it was it was a relief thinking that she wasn't in Gaza I
preferred that happy to say that despite the fact that the harsh conditions they
have been under and the experience of captivity they did not require any
emergent medical intervention who hundred trucks we did not reach till now 70
trucks also according to the release of the prisoners we believe that the
Israelis are manipulating the issue we will stand against that and we are still
waiting the response of the mediatars
He's okay.
I'm so excited.
I thought he was really okay.
He asked if he came to a restaurant?
He said he didn't go there anymore.
He said he didn't eat this.
He didn't eat this, but he said that he was in the same way.
What about you?
He didn't get the restaurant, so I didn't get the restaurant.
We have a lot of people who want to know how to do it,
and how to do it, and how to do it, and how to do it.
Now, let's say that we will always be able to stop the situation
that we have in this situation.
And let's say that we will be able to do it,
and we will be able to do it in our lives.
The period of time is short.
It doesn't take weeks.
It takes days, a little bit more, a little bit less.
Every process and duration will be done.
That is, if we want to continue to do it in the next time,
it will be when the pieces are broken,
the pieces are broken, the pieces are broken,
and the forces are broken.
This is the basis.